[{"answer": "He just crushed it, Matthew.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "How did you find it?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "I did, yes.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "ORGAN: Did you enjoy it?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Have you ever met one who isn't?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Well as in somebody who's not necessarily in the entertainment game, he's not famous as a celebrity but has real power.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Well, now when you say powerful, what do you mean by that?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Well, they go like and hang on about how awful fame is and they moan away about it all.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "And they say they don't want any of it?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "ACON: Well, yes.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "But, I've seen you beyond this a few times saying, you know what -- everybody wants to be famous, right?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Here's the thing -- I mean, I don't act for statues.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "It's exactly how I would be feeling, if I had made 50 films of the quality you have and I still haven't had my moment, seeing some of the clowns that walk away with those gardens (ph) -- I mean, it's going to get to you, isn't it?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "I was kidding.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Was that a joke?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "You know, it was recommended that we -- we put, you know, some money with him and we did.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "How did you get caught -- how did you get caught up in the whole Madoff thing?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Have you said how much?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "ACON: I'd rather not say.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "I mean, at the absolute peak of your time with Madoff, how much did you think you had?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Wow, that's a good question.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "Without giving the amount, what was the percentage of -- of your wealth that was committed to this?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "It wasn't good.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "I mean, this is horrendous, isn't it?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "Got a call, you know.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "What was the moment you knew that this was all going belly up?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Did you get any money back at all?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "Well, I think that it's a good way to think about what you have to be grateful for.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "In terms of a life realignment -- what did it do to you and your wife and as a family do you think, in terms of how you now look at life?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "Yes, she's a knockout.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "I mean, you -- you've done well, haven't you?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "Yes, Clay.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Clay Bertrand?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Sexual purposes?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Twenty dollars each time.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "Did he pay you for this?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "Well, it's tough.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "What was Hollywood like when you go through the dry out process?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Well, you know, there's -- there's a great line in a -- that Martin Short has in a movie that we're doing -- he plays my agent and things aren't -- I'm a -- I'm a director in the movie and things aren't going well and his -- his character says, \"Well, frankly everyone wants to distance themselves from the stench.\"", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "When you've tasted some real glory?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "Yes, it's six degrees.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "Only six?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "Fascinating.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "How about that?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Well, the charitable way that you've done this.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "That idea?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "Do you see evidence that it works?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, I think that we have a long way to go in terms of our specific site.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "When you make people think like that?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Pretty cool, right?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Well, the truth is, is that I was doing a play down in the Village in -- a real long time ago, and I had a matinee and an evening performance and during -- after the matinee, I went to the deli and I was buying a sandwich.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "How did you meet?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "Well, then, years later --", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "ORGAN: What -- and how did you then get together?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "Years later?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "But has she said she harbored some weird thought about you since that deli moment?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "Did you know she was the one?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "Well, I'd never actually seen the statistics that there's any more divorce in show business than there is in any other thing.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "What is -- what is the reason why so many show business marriages flounder, do you think?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, I don't -- I don't know.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "How have you managed to resist the lure of the groupie, for lack of a better phrase?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it's weird.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "How would you feel if your kids wanted to get into the business?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I've heard you don't ever watch your films.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "You never rewatch an old movie?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Just there's so much that I feel like I wish I'd done differently that it's kind of like torture.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "You're such a perfectionist that you just see so many things you wish you'd done in a different way?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "And it's just too much agony, you can't watch it?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Oh.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "What is the one Kevin Bacon movie, if I forced you to watch again at gunpoint, you would watch?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Is that the dream role for you?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Well, exactly.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Well, you don't -- you're not happy you're middle-aged until, I guess, you're middle-aged because what other choice do you have?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "That's a terrible gift.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Have any of you three discussed colonoscopies with your friends over a few beers?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Well, I got that idea because I saw on the -- either Letterman or whatever.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I mean, in my mind I'm not above, you know, five and twenty.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "Are you sort of resistant to be tagged with them here?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "It's not bad at all.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "What's the worst thing about getting middle-aged?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Well, I think we really appreciate it.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Well, I don't -- I keep -- my biggest problem is I think that I'm still -- I'm not middle-aged and that I'm 20 years younger.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Or do you see some negatives in the aging process?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Well, you mentally feel it.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "You don't age as much in the mirror, do you?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Andre talked about you learn about life more, so when you get to middle age, you can almost appreciate the reality of life.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "How am I old?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "Well, you get perspective.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "Is that something -- do you learn enough that you start to appreciate what life really is?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "Whoa.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "What's been the biggest mistake you've ever made?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "I hope it's a good one because we could use a story idea.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "Ray?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "I regret things hour to hour, you know.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Or do you have genuine look back and think, yeah, that was a deciding moment?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "The one with all the women.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "What are you talking about?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "When you were falling about laughing there watching your own show, which is always encouraging.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "You quite like this new stage of your life, right?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "Oh lord.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "If you could give advice to a 16-year-old Ray Romano, what would you tell him?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "A 16-year-old Ray Romano?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "Oh, I had in my 20s, I didn't know what I wanted to do, and my brother had just gotten married, and he moved out of the house.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "What kind of thing?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "Yeah, I had like a very anxiety-ridden, and I had a little emotional struggle there for like a year or two in my 20s.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "Had one in the 30s too?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "Oh, a young Scott.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "Scott, what would you say, if you were talking to a young Scott, what would you tell him?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "I'm being quiet now.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "You must have had some wild days?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "It's essential, I think.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "How important is it to find the right woman?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "No, I do not Twitter.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "Do you Twitter?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "I would say from the past, or not even -- Sophia Loren.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "Who would you say?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "I'll go for Marilyn Monroe.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "Any of you going to go for the classic middle aged crisis?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "None of you are going for the classic stereotypical middle aged crisis woman.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 713, "question": "Can I take Marilyn?", "qSentId": 712}, {"answer": "She is still alive.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 723, "question": "Why did he get Sophia Loren?", "qSentId": 722}, {"answer": "It was movie that never came out.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 730, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 729}, {"answer": "But I watch it every night.", "docId": "110610pmt", "aSentId": 732, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 731}]